Hello everyone, this is Rian Akita, Ai Yamaguchi, Ai Kinoshita, Aoi Anno, and Riko Iwamoto, from the blue sky I've always wanted to see.
I'm Misato Miyagashi, Riko Iwamoto, and this is the ng word game.
We'll have a conversation based on the theme of the talk, and the winner is the last one to get the other person's ng word or action out of the conversation.
The winner is the last one to finish the game!
I was really looking forward to it, but I didn't think about it, I didn't think about strategy, I didn't think about it, I didn't think about it, I had it, I think I'm writing about the finished product now without thinking about it.
I think I'm writing the finished product without thinking about it right now, and I think that's why I'm going to go to standard Japanese, and I'm going to speak in honorifics and stuff.
I think it's a good strategy.
I'm not sure if it's my part or not.
I'm not just a raw Meguro, I'm a big boy!
Boo boo!
Boo boo boo... let's say it's a game...
It's been a while since I've lived in a boom before a boom. I can't say anything about it.
I've been into going to the movies lately!
I'm addicted to going to the movies a I know I've said it a million times above, but I feel like I like what's going on.
I've started to like internet mysteries and scary movies... and surprisingly, I like Harry Potter.
I love Harry Potter, I love Harry Potter, I love Harry Potter, I love Harry Potter
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I love Harry Potter, I love Harry Potter, I love Harry Potter.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'm getting better and better
I'm waiting for you to tell me that I've won, I'm in, Harry, I love you if you tell me about your book
I'd love it if we could talk about Harry's book.
I'm looking for four clovers, and I'm wondering if you've heard this one before.
I've heard you say that you find a lot of things, and not a lot of them, but I've been able to change that and find something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, wow.
Okay, so I'll let you guys get to it. No, no, no, no, no.
Start start with a picture of a beer or a pool or a picture of Liam in the sky, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to take something third place, second place, and then we'll see what the sky looks like today, okay?
me... there seems to be a lack of caution.
Let's do it.
Let's do it!
Iron flying Talos
boo boo
I want to dream about what will happen to me, but I don't want to be like this. I'd like to dream that I'll be like this, but I don't want to be like this.
I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now... I'm going to do it now!
I'll see you someday.
I love you so much!
ah?
I love it so much!
I'll predict it for you, too.
Riko's a bit naive, so I probably gave her a hint earlier that she doesn't have to speak in Kansai.
I'm feeling a little Kansai-ben, so why don't you move yourself along?
I'm usually like that, so I've changed my game.
I've changed... come here!
It's okay, you can change your mind now.
If I notice Yuan, I'll cut out the last one.
What?
That's right...
Oh, yeah...
but still...
ar сказала no, I mean as a compliment
Oh, what the heck!
Well then, for the second theme, the last minute, if you win, you're 4chan, so congratulations!
I think we can crush two people at once at the Janger Cafe!
Okay, the second theme is "I have a story"...
I'm sure it's going to be a lot of fun!
But I really like Lianne's theme.
I love the theme of "I like this.
I love it... I love it... I love it... I love it... I love it... I love it...
LOL!
I can't do it.
Okay, here we go.
There's a lot of miming going on here.
I have this image of everyone imitating Yuna-chan's part of the song for you by Sakumogumi.
I have this image of you imitating Yuna-chan's part of the song.
How's that? You're right.
Me too.
What do you think?
We all get along.
Are you a spider or a spider? What were they doing?
Oh... Ah!
Ah!
I've had it!
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I'm going to say "too much" right on target, aren't I?
I don't know, some out-of-towner ate me, you know?
I'm going to have to ask you to confirm that you're still in the game.
I'm going to do 8 things for 2 points and get 2 points.
How about 8 for 2 points?
Okay, the last topic will be memories from the live show.
There you are!
The third round is ready!
I don't know...
The moment we went out on stage, the view was amazing.
The people...
I was really moved.
I was moved at first, wasn't I?
I was moved.
It was very moving.
Wait a minute.
I was impressed.
Yes, it was.
You know... maybe I have a strong image of UB1.
I like Aoi's family too.
I always like the yellow bird's name.
Saito-san, right?
No, what is it?
Is it this one?
That name...
Mr. Shimizu, right?
That's right.
Who else?
There was someone else.
But the name always reminds me of him
Is it that long?
I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll never know. You never know.
That's it.
That's it!
Aoi told us to like her.
I don't know...
It wasn't a boom.
Yes, it was.
That song.
YUN&TETSUI
Spider group...
We all did it.
We did it, we did it, we did it.
When it was distributed
Thank you.
Yeah? Yeah?
Isn't he cool?
It's cool.
Yeah, it is.
Face the camera.
Aoi's.
Nice!
It's not like she's going to say "I want you to like me" or something.
It's okay.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'm sure it's fine.
Achy.
Make me like you.
It's okay.
I'm glad.
It's so good.
I want to hear it from Leanne.
I want you to like it.
No, I don't.
Can we do it this way?
Is that a deal?
But, you know, I don't care how many patterns we do. But, you know, I don't care how many patterns there are.
But you're right.
Be yourself.
Let's see what you can do.
Let's all do it.
I'm doing it.
You're gonna love it.
Come on. - Come on.
Come on.
That's it.
Let's just go home.
He said he's going to change it to "like me" or something.
Let's do it this way, just for the sake of it.
That's great!
But personally, I think ViniLive is great.
Like the ViniLive handshake events.
I was able to go to a lot of places, so it was a lot of fun.
Hokkaido made me happy.
What do you think this is?
It was kind of happy.
I thought it was something like that.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
There are people who shake hands in different ways.
Normally, it's like this.
Or like this.
Like this?
But they do it like this.
I'm not like this.
Okay, bye.
What is it?
Lisnia. Lisnia.
What?
Okay, then.
So that's what this is about.
I was just trying to figure out which one to do, and it was really appealing.
Then you blew it.
So that's what you're saying.
What blew?
I've not only shaken hands like this, but also with my fingers.
What kind of handshake?
Yes! What?
That's weird!
What?
What is it?
Oh, my God!
Wait, wait, wait.
That's great!
Okay, come on, it's like four against two, so let's just say we're all on the same team, and there's something...
There's something big in there, isn't there?
I was so surprised, but I also showed you a horror movie... 3 horror movies...
3 horror movies...
What a surprise!
He's just saying "boo-boo"... when he's trying to get me to say something... but I can't tell by the look in his eyes.
You've got that bitter, melancholy look in your eyes when you're trying to get me to say something.